=No.9 Hunter=
=Episode 18=
(Stab yourselves with your swords.)
(Die to live.)
(That breaks the illusion.)
(Ziyan,)
(If you cannot find the Twin Hands,)
(there is one final option.)
(Use your life as a bridge.)
(Let the Wind God Chronicle
merge with the Stone inside her.)
(She will gain the Chronicle's power)
(and separate from the Divine Stone.)
(The sky will be mended.)
(She will live.)
(But you)
(will perish.)
Yuanchu.
What are you doing?
Stop this right now!
Stop!
Please stop!
Stop this!
This time,
once again,
with my life,
I trade for yours.
No!
Yuanchu,
Yuanchu, are you all right?
I love you.
You wretched pair!
How dare you scheme against me!
Your greed is boundless.
In the end, you'll have nothing.
Very well.
I will take both the Divine Stone
and the Wind God Chronicle for myself.
What...
What is happening?
Thunder.
Hahaha!
You still dare to fight me?
Hmph.
Purestone Bloom.
The Chronicle and the Stone have fused.
Chi Xiao of the Demon Hunting Bureau,
dares to betray me?
I serve the land and its people.
Not one person's greed.
Fine. Since you ask for it,
I will grant your wish.
I will grind you both to dust.
My flesh. My bones. You shall not pass.
You dare obstruct my great work?
You dare oppose me?
Delusional!
I told you before.
The Divine Stone
and both realms are mine.
Thunder strikes!
Chi Xiao!
- Chi Xiao, hold on!
- Chi Xiao!
Are you alright?
Thunderdragon Strike.
A move that can only be used once
in a lifetime.
This time,
I have finally protected you.
Hold on.
There must be another way.
Stay with me.
Hmph.
It is no use.
Chi Xiao!
I'm sorry...
this is as far
as I can go.
No.
If there is a next life,
I hope
I get to meet you first.
(Chi Xiao, you should smile more often.)
(Just like this.)
(Look, Chi Xiao.)
Let me
stand by your side.
Will you let me?
Will you?
Chi Xiao!
You're going to be fine.
- Chi Xiao!
Chi Xiao!
Traitor.
At least you died for something.
Chi Xiao!
I will take your life
to avenge Chi Xiao!
Heaven and earth, grant me power.
Strike down evil!
Hmph.
You can't die yet.
In that case,
I will show you
what the Twin Hands can truly do.
So you can die knowing the truth.
Ah!
Ziyan!
Mm.
Stop!
Ziyan!
I've done it.
I've done it!
Hahaha!
The world is mine!
Both realms are mine to command!
Hahaha!
Yu Linjun?
♪I drink the rain of this mortal world,
and seek the path I chose♪
♪How much sorrow and joy have I known?♪
♪With this flesh and blood,
I chase the distant light♪
♪Just to see clearly
the memories of this drifting life♪
♪Let the wind sweep away
this heavy air of sorrow♪
♪Do not forget the tangled paths
that you and I have crossed♪
♪Let towering waves come crashing down;
I'll fight against the tide♪
♪I shatter
the hollow fate they wrote for me♪
♪With a heart free of regret,
I'll face the heavens and earth♪